[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
[Emilia] Get out of here!
I will bury my own husband!
What are you doing? Show Dad some respect.
How dare you go against your own mother!
Did you hit your head again?
Want me to tell everyone
the truth about you?! Huh?!
Do you really want to bury your husband?
Then go rest in peace!
[Emilia] Why are you bringing me here?
[Julio] Your lunacy isn't doing us
any good anymore.
Mama, why am I here?
Raul, Papa's at it again.
He's always doing this to me.
[Julio] I assure you the whole
province of Ardiente
will be under my control
if I can take over
Helena Montoya's organization.
And what makes you think
we'll hand it over to you?
I am the only ally of Helena to Ardiente.
Then give me the password.
[Arnaldo] What are you guys up to?
I think we're being followed.
We have to lose them, Jepoy.
[Arnaldo] You can't run from me.
[Anna] Jepoy, watch out for that truck!
[driver] Hey, watch where you're going!
[Arnaldo] You can run, but you can't hide.
[Lily] Starting tomorrow,
I will be Diego's wife.
[Arnaldo] I want your men to
search Poblacion Ardiente
for a white van with this plate number.
I'll be gone for a while.
So, it'll be just you
and Grandpa for a while.
Help him take over Grandma's syndicate.
Everything's going to be fine.
[soft music playing]
[soft music continues playing]
[bright instrumental playing]
Nanny Loring…
Uncle Pandoy…
Dad…
Please join me
on this special day in my life.
Someday, we'll all meet again.
Dad, please join us
as Diego and I start
our new lives together.
Okay. Thank you. Go inside for now.
[phone ringing]
Well?
Mayor, we've tracked them down.
They're at the St. Monica chapel
in Rosario.
Okay. Thank you.
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
["Sa'Yo" instrumental continues]
-Hey, don't jump! Hey!
-[young Diego screams]
[young Lily] If it weren't for me,
you would've fallen off the cliff.
[young Diego] Who are you? Wonder Woman?
[young Lily] No. My name is Lily.
[young Diego] Lily…
Thanks for helping me out.
[young Lily] No worries. I got you!
Thank you, Lily!
You're welcome, Diego. [giggles]
Let's go.
[townsfolk cheering]
[Pandoy] The one and only
Diego Ardiente-Torillo!
[Lily] It's Diego. That's him.
My best friend.
[stutters] For you.
[Lily] I really wanted
to tell him everything.
But then I thought,
if he finds out the truth,
he'll hate me.
It's better this way.
Just let Lily live in his memory.
Lily is just a memory to me and Diego.
[Diego] I can't explain it.
Whenever we're together,
I feel like I'm with Lily again.
By being with you.
Do you think it's a bad thing
that Ivy reminds me so much of Lily?
I just noticed they have
so many similarities.
How she pinches Butchoy's cheeks.
How she likes pinwheels.
Her reaction when I took her to Lily's
old house and the secret garden.
And now this.
Why is she helping us?
[Loring] Let's say that she is Lily.
Then why does she need to pretend?
[Diego] That's what I have to find out.
-[Lily] Diego!
-[Diego] Ivy?
Diego, help us, please!
My mother needs help, please!
Answer me right now.
Are Ivy Aguas and Lily Cruz
the same person?
Yes, Diego.
I'm your old friend. I'm Lily.
[Diego] Ivy, whatever your plans
are, I'm here for you.
Because I love you.
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
[Diego] Ivy, I don't care
how powerful they are.
Nothing is impossible when I'm with you.
That's why I believe that
we can get through all this.
Stop the wedding!
Hurry!
Ivy, I'm right here. We did it!
Ivy, I want you to be happy.
I want you to be free of this burden.
And I hope I'll be there with you.
[Lily] Diego, I love you.
[Diego] Ivy, I'll do everything
I can to put an end to this.
I'll make sure your plans succeed.
Even if it costs me my life,
I won't let anything happen to you.
[Lily] Thank you.
Thank you for keeping your promise to me…
that you'd help my plans succeed.
I hope you'll be with me
till the very end.
I know we're in
the middle of a war, Diego.
But I think it's worth the fight
when you aren't alone.
From now on,
let's make it official.
Will you be mine?
Yes. I'm all yours.
[Diego] We've been through so much.
And so many people have tried
to come between us.
And yet, here we are, stronger than ever.
Our love is going
to last a lifetime, Lily.
There's no turning back.
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary
continues playing]
[song fading]
[tense music building]
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
Remember that chubby
childhood friend of yours?
The crybaby?
You're the one who helped him.
You're the one who taught
him how to be strong.
You're the one who
taught him how to fight.
And that's why he's here,
standing in front of you,
fighting for his love for you.
Lily, no matter how many times I fall,
no matter how many times I get hurt…
I'll never stop loving you.
I love you so much, Lily.
And I swear…
that I'm going to love you
until my last breath.
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
I grew up…
with a hardened heart.
But you…
you're the one who made me feel,
and showed me that…
there are still good people in this world.
Diego, you're the reason…
I learned to love again.
Thank you…
for teaching me how to love.
Thank you for loving me…
even though it's so difficult.
That's why you, and the love we share…
are among the very few
good things going on
in my life right now.
I'm so happy right now, Diego.
I love you so much.
I really do.
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary
continues playing]
[priest] Diego…
do you take Lily to be
your lawfully wedded wife,
your other half, to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better or worse,
in sickness and in health,
to love and cherish forevermore?
I do, Father.
[priest] Lily…
do you take Diego to be
your lawfully wedded husband,
your other half, to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better or worse,
in sickness and in health,
to love and cherish forevermore?
I do, Father. I do.
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary
continues playing]
[song fading]
[ominous music building]
[cocks gun]
Lily, I offer you this ring…
as a symbol of my eternal love
and faithfulness to you.
[suspenseful music playing]
Diego, wear this ring…
as a symbol of my eternal love
and faithfulness to you.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone vibrating]
GRANDPA
As a representative of the church,
I hereby authorize
and bless your marriage.
Now, you may kiss the bride.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
[applause]
[song fading]
[tense music playing]
[groaning]
[mumbles] This isn't happening.
This isn't happening.
No, you're not gonna get everything.
No, you're not gonna get a happy ending.
[indistinct]
No. No. No! No!
No!
No. Wake up. Wake up! Wake up.
You suffered because of them.
[line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
Hello, Grandpa.
Arnaldo, where are you?
I found Lily and Diego.
And guess what? They just got married.
I wasn't invited.
Well then, you better leave
before someone sees you there.
You know what's funny here?
I thought I had them fooled.
I thought I gained their trust.
I was wrong.
The joke's on me.
I'm the idiot.
Come home. Leave them there.
I promise you.
We'll get back at them
when the time is right.
Grandpa, I'm sorry I failed you again.
But I want to thank you
for always taking care of me.
[ominous music]
I love you.
And I love you too, my son.
You always remember that.
Now, come home.
We'll have a couple of drinks
and enjoy the night, okay?
I'll be waiting.
Bye, Grandpa.
[cocks gun]
[happy music playing]
[Lily] Hello!
[Camia] They're here!
[applause]
[Diego] Careful.
[glasses clinking]
-[Lily] Do you want us to kiss?
-[Camia] Yeah.
-[Jepoy] Kiss!
-[Marlon] Kiss!
Okay. You liked that, huh?
[uplifting instrumental playing]
[glasses clinking]
[applause]
-Have a big bite!
-Do it at the same time.
[applause]
-[Camia] Cheers or kiss?
-[Marlon] Cheers.
[Diego] I hear kiss. Kiss.
[Diego] Remember that chubby
childhood friend of yours?
[priest] You may now kiss the bride.
[applause]
Thank you.
[Camia] Lily, dear, Diego…
I'm so happy for you both.
Despite all your hardships,
you still managed to fulfill your dreams.
So, promise me you'll both
take care of each other, okay?
I promise, Mom.
I promise.
What about you guys?
Aren't you going to give us a hug?
-Group hug?
-Give us a group hug.
-Everybody.
-Thanks, everyone.
[upbeat instrumental playing]
Thank you for making this
the happiest day of my life.
I think I'm the happiest
and luckiest guy on earth.
Thank you…
Mrs. Lily Cruz-Torillo.
-It sounds nice.
-Hmm.
Lily Cruz-Torillo.
I'm really happy too.
Let's enjoy the night.
Because first thing tomorrow,
we'll continue working towards our dream
of having a peaceful and happy town.
We will live in Ardiente.
We'll raise our children here.
We'll start a family here.
And no one will ever have
to experience the suffering
we've endured
at the hands of the Ardientes.
Your dream is my dream too.
And my battles are your battles too.
Remember, Diego.
It's you and me. Till the end.
[romantic instrumental playing]
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary
continues playing]
[song fading]
[suspenseful music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
Lily… Hello…
Dad?
Yes, Lily. It's me.
Dad!
Dad, what are you doing here?
Lily, I'm so happy you've
finally found the one for you.
But be careful, okay?
You still have enemies around.
Never leave each other's side.
Of course, Dad.
Lily, your lives are in danger. Wake up.
[ominous music]
[thunder rumbling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[glass shattering]
[Arnaldo] Leave Diego! It's just us now.
So, you're all mine. You're all mine!
Get your hands off my wife!
[Lily] As long as you live, no one
will ever love you, Arnaldo!
No one! Because you're a monster!
And even if you let me live,
I will never love you!
I will never love a criminal!
-[screams]
-[gunshot]
It came from the governor's mansion!
I am coming for you!
I will be coming for each
and every one of you!
[theme music playing]